(Sheldon:)...of gamma rays
from dark-matter annihilations.
(Sheldon:)-It occurred to me that I could--
-Excuse me.
(Leonard:)How many reels before the subordinate
male protagonist gets to his point?
(Sheldon:)If you didn't cheer at my entrance,
it's too late to buy into the premise.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, I got some extra money
from the head of the department...
(Sheldon:)...and Raj can come work for me.
(Raj:)You want me to work with you?
(Sheldon:)For me.
(Sheldon:)You're going to have to listen
more carefully when you're on the job.
Okay. Please don't take this
the wrong way...
...but I'd rather swim buck naked
across the Ganges...
(Raj:)...with a paper cut on my nipple...
(Raj:)...and die a slow, agonizing death
from a viral infection...
(Raj:)...than work with you.
(Sheldon:)For me.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Raj(knocking and entering):)Sheldon, are you busy?
(Sheldon:)Of course I'm busy.